zylom.com 2008-06-25

# zylom: Privacy Policy

Zylom is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of Internet users' data.

## Non-personally identifiable information

Zylom does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as your browser type or the type of computer operating system you use.

## Personally identifiable information

Besides this, Zylom also collects personally identifiable information. This information is stored when you register for the game channel or use other services within the game channel. This information is used to provide customized content, advertising, and for other means.

## Cookies

This game channel requires the use of cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you'll find cookies at most major web sites. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web site and is stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are used in this game channel to enhance the user experience.

## Sharing of information

As we reserve the right to use personal data, we can send out newsletters. Go to My Details (on the top of the web site) if you do not wish to receive our newsletters. To do this, you must first log in. If you become a member of this game site, you automatically grant us permission to share your personal data with selected third parties.

## Types of e-mails

Zylom will send you e-mails to inform you of the launch of new games. From time to time Zylom may also send you an e-mail to inform you of a special offer. In addition if you purchase a game or FunPass subscription Zylom will send you an e-mail to confirm receipt of any monies. You can unsubscribe from any communication at any time from <https://secure2.zylom.com/myaccount/2/>

If these do not answer all your questions please contact our customer sevice department on [support@zylom.com](mailto:support@zylom.com)

## Changes in the privacy policy

Zylom may amend this policy from time to time. Changes will be published on this page.
